Firefox Private Network Browser Extension (Beta) Privacy Notice
===============================================================

Archived, June 16, 2023

Version 3.0, effective July 7, 2020

At Mozilla, we design products with your privacy in mind.

Firefox Private Network (FPN) protects your device’s web connections. Mozilla partners with Cloudflare to privately and securely encrypt your web traffic within Firefox.

This privacy notice explains what data FPN collects, shares, and why. We also adhere to the [Mozilla Privacy Policy](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/privacy/) for how we receive, handle, and share information.

Things you should know:
-----------------------

### Information we collect

**Firefox Account Information.** This service requires a Firefox Account, which sends FPN your email address, locale, and IP address. Learn more about [Firefox Account data practices](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/privacy/firefox/#firefox-accounts).

**Location information.** Firefox FPN receives your IP address from your Firefox Account when you sign up for and use the service. We use the IP address in order to approximate your location because FPN is currently only available in the United States.

**Technical data.** Mozilla receives basic information from FPN about your mobile and desktop app version and device, including device operating system and hardware configuration. When FPN sends data to us, your IP address is temporarily collected as part of our server logs.

**Interaction data.** Mozilla receives data about your interactions with FPN, such as when you enable and disable the proxy and the amount of bandwidth you use when the proxy is enabled.

Read the technical and interaction data collection documentation [here](https://github.com/mozilla/secure-proxy/blob/master/docs/metrics.md). We use the data we collect to improve performance and stability for our users, and to measure FPN’s performance.

### Information we share

FPN shares data with certain third parties in order to provide the service to you. Mozilla has written agreements in place with these companies contractually obligating them to protect your information. Here’s who we use:

**Cloudflare.** As you browse, Firefox will encrypt the data you send to websites and send it to Cloudflare. Cloudflare will also receive your computer’s IP address, the IP address of the site you are browsing to, the timestamp, and a unique identifier. Cloudflare does not share this data with others and deletes this after 24 hours unless necessary for its security or legal obligations. Learn more at [Cloudflare’s Privacy Notice](https://www.cloudflare.com/mozilla/firefox-private-network-privacy-notice/).

**Stripe.** Mozilla uses Stripe to process your payment information. Mozilla receives a record of your subscription and information about the status of your account’s subscription and payment. Mozilla does not receive or store your payment card details. You can learn more about Stripe’s data practices by reading their [Global Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
